const quizQuestions = [
    {
        "question" : "If you have access to Material Non-Public Information or inside information, you are considered as a Covered employee.",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
        ],
        "answer" : "True"
    },
    {
        "question" : "If you're a covered employee, you need to disclose all your brokerage accounts with _____ days if onboarding.",
        "options": ["15","30","45","60"],
        "answer" : "30"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Dormant accounts are deemed to be inactive and can be exempted from disclosure.",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer" : "False"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Prefered brokers are:",
        "options": [ "ICICI and Kotak securities", "ICICI and Axis securities", "HDFC and Kotak securities", "HDFC and Axis securities" ],
        "answer" : "HDFC and Kotak securities",
    },
    {
        "question" : "Preclearance is not applicable on Mutual funds and Gold bonds.",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer" : "True"
    },
    {
        "question" : "You can seek exception for Intra-day trading.",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer" : "False"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Preclearance approval is valid for:",
        "options": ["Current day","Next Trading day","Current and next trading day","Any day since you already got the approval."],
        "answer" : "Current and next trading day"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Holding period requirement for any asset you buy is:",
        "options": ["10","30","7","25"],
        "answer" : "30"
    },
    {
        "question" : "I am a non covered employee and I own a side hustle business outside CITI. CITI doesn't know about it. Do I need to disclose it?",
        "options": ["Yes","No"],
        "answer" : "No"
    },
    {
        "question" : "For preferred brokers, statements are not required to be uploaded.",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer" : "False"
    },

];

export default quizQuestions;